Amanda Watson

123 Your Street, Austin, TX 12345 youremail@exampie.com (123) 456-7890

A Supply Chain Analyst with seven years of experience, specializing in supply chain management, procurement, change management, and organizational leadership. A strong history of building and managing cross-function a I teams to refine procurement and fulfillment processes. Adept at performing complex business analysis to reduce costs across the supply chain.

Education

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Supply Chain Management University Of Austin, Austin, TX September 2010 - May 2014

Key Skills

- Supply Chain Management
- Cross-functional Leadership
- ♦ Change Management
- Procurement
- Project M a na g e ment
- Vendor Management
- Contract Negotiation

Certifications

- Certified Business Analysis Professional (CBAP), 2018
- Six Sigma Green Belt, 2017
- Certified Supply Chain Professional (CSCP), 2015

Professional Experience

Senior Supply Chain Analyst

Fleet Management Solutions Inc., Austin, TX I July 2017 - Present

- Manage a cross-functional team of 15 procurement specialists, data analysts, and supply chain coordinators to execute process improvement projects, which improved lead time by 18% and resulted in a \$200K reduction in annual procurement costs
- Coordinate with the purchasing department to analyze inventory pricing, identify vendors, perform contract negotiations, and define sourcing strategies
- Analyze KPIs and supply chain data and deliver presentations to C-level executives and senior leadership on supplier performance

Supply Chain Analyst

Arlington Manufacturing Corp,, Austin,TX | June 2014 - July 2017

- Defined sourcing and fulfilment strategy, managed vendor relationships, conducted pricing negotiations, and reduced procurement costs by \$150K
- Partnered with the supply chain manager to lead process improvement initiatives and enhance supply chain performance, which included defining new fleet management procedures to generate a 25% reduction in transportation costs